[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"TIME": ["this morning", "this morning"]}, "docId": "120824pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", ",", ":", "NNP", ":", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "NN", "VBD", "VBG", "PRP", "RB", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", ",", "IN", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 19, "question": "What happened?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 20, "answer": "You know, actually, (INAUDIBLE) this morning, because when I woke up this morning, for some reason, something was telling me not to go to work, like something told me to call the company and tell them I couldn't come in.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Green Line"]}, "docId": "120824pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 50, "question": "What did you see?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 51, "answer": "I was coming up from the Green Line.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120824pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 77, "question": "Would you think that's probably right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "POS", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 78, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120824pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "TO", "PRP$", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 108, "question": "Did anybody at any stage -- did your brother ever say he had a problem with this guy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ":", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 109, "answer": "No, my brother is -- you know, he's such a loving uncle to his nieces and nephews.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "120824pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 119, "question": "What do you feel about guns in America right now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 120, "answer": "You know, I don't think this is a referendum on guns in America.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120824pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 144, "question": "IULIANI, FORMER NYC MAYOR (via telephone): How are you, Piers?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NN", ":", ":", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 145, "answer": "Fine.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120824pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", ":", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "NN", "NN", ",", "DT", "DT", "CD", "CC", "DT", "CD", "WDT", "VBD", "NN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 158, "question": "What do you think should happen?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 159, "answer": "Well, you know, I think these -- the situations are not the right situations to pick to debate gun control, either this one or the one that took place a couple weeks ago.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120824pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 194, "question": "Be honest, Rudy, do you think that was a little below the belt?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VB", "VBN", ",", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 195, "answer": "No, but I think it was not the most tasteful joke.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Rudy"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120824pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 210, "question": "Are you excited about the convention, Rudy, or are you slightly apprehensive?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 211, "answer": "Oh, well, I'm only apprehensive because of the storm.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Rudy"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120824pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 250, "question": "Were you as shocked as everybody else seems to have been when he threw the towel in?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 251, "answer": "Yes, he gave up.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Marion Jones"]}, "docId": "120824pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "NNP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "CD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 262, "question": "What's the informed reaction?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "VBN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 263, "answer": "Marion Jones never failed a drug test and she is known as one of the great cheaters of our time.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120824pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 273, "question": "Do you think, Christine, there's any doubt Lance Armstrong was a cheat?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 274, "answer": "Well, I'm a journalist.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Christine", "Lance Armstrong"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120824pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 310, "question": "You don't do things by halves, do you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 311, "answer": "No, I love big challenges.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120824pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", ",", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 327, "question": "Do you think either Romney or Obama has been courageous enough with their plan for the economy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "JJ", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 328, "answer": "I think it's too early to know, quite frankly.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120824pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 346, "question": "-- and taking a little wager that the American will reward them for that patriotic hit on their balance sheet by going out and buying more products?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "CC", "VBG", "DT", "RB", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "CC", "NN", "RBR", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 347, "answer": "Yes, I think it's an interesting idea.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Apple"], "PERSON": ["Steve"]}, "docId": "120824pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "NNP", "TO", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 360, "question": "When you were given the task by Steve Jobs of creating the Apple Store, what was the philosophy that you really wanted to create?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 361, "answer": "Well, you know, when we launched the Apple Store, Steve knew that for Apple to win, it was going to win on innovation.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Apple Store"], "PERSON": ["Steve Jobs"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120824pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 448, "question": "Now how many failures did you have to go through first?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "RP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 449, "answer": "You had hundreds and hundreds and hundreds, as I recall.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120824pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "DT", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 494, "question": "Awkward to do that on camera, or are you two just such shameless exhibitionists that it just came naturally?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "IN", "NN", ",", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "CD", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 495, "answer": "When we're not on set, we're often in a park just putting it all out there.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120824pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 551, "question": "Did you know about this when you met?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 552, "answer": "Not when we first met, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120824pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP$", "RB", "NN", "IN", "VBD", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "VBD", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 580, "question": "How did you, in the end, get the self-determination to get yourself out of it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "NN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 581, "answer": "Well, my only obsession that was stronger than that was working.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["California"]}, "docId": "120824pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 627, "question": "Is this true, that you waited for same sex marriage to be endorsed before you took the plunge yourselves?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "JJ", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 628, "answer": "In California specifically.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120824pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 649, "question": "Are you both, I'm guessing, Obama supporters?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", ",", "NNP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 650, "answer": "Yeah, we're liberals.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120824pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ":"], "qSentId": 651, "question": "ORGAN: What does the prospect of a Romney presidency do to you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "VBP", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 652, "answer": "Will it --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120824pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 666, "question": "In what respect?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 667, "answer": "Any respect you like.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Putin"], "LOCATION": ["Russia"]}, "docId": "120824pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "``", "NN", "NNP", "''", "WRB", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 668, "question": "What do you think of your country?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 669, "answer": "I'll tell you, I read in \"Vanity Fair\" how Putin dealt with some of his adversaries in Russia.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120824pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 680, "question": "Be honest?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 681, "answer": "I didn't.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]